噢，你用乒乓球打败麦克真的太帅了。 你想要…那个吗？
The way you crushed Mike at Ping-Pong was such a turn-on. You wanna..?
呃，我是想，不过我有点累了
You know,I'd love to,but I'm a little tired.
- 我会用枕套把头包住的。 - 那来吧！
- I'll put a pillowcase over my head. - You're on.
- 嗨！ - 有事吗？
- Hey. - What's up?
麦克在洗澡 顺便说一下，我们还没有做那个...
Well,Mike's taking a shower,which,by the way,there's no law against.
我想去吃点东西，所以如果你们也想…
And then we're gonna grab some food. So if you want..
那是罗斯吗？
- Finally. - Is that Ross?
是啊，那面破墙什么声音都包不住。
Yeah. You can hear everything through these stupid walls.
- 好象有人和他一起。 - 应该没有吧
- Sounds like he's with someone. - He could be alone.
今天早上我听见他做俯卧撑 后来还跟他的三头肌说话。
This morning I heard him do pushups and then talk to his triceps.
等等，我想菲比是对的。
Wait a minute,I think Phoebe's right.
我也听见有人和他在一起。
Yeah,I hear someone else in there with him.
- 盖勒博士！ - 天呐，太不可思议了…
- Dr. Geller! - God,you're amazing.
我刚想让你这样称呼我呢。
I didn't even have to ask you to call me that.
- 噢，天呐，是查莉！ - 她背着乔伊和罗斯乱搞！
- Oh,my God,that's Charlie! - She's cheating on Joey with Ross!
噢，那个尖酸刻薄的…大…荡妇…
Oh,that tart! Floozy! Giant!
- 我不应该这样 - 对，你是对的。
- I'm not sure about this. - Yeah,you're right.
这根本不关我们的事。
This is none of our business.
不，我应该找个方法好好的偷听。 给我个玻璃杯！
I'm not sure it's the best way to hear everything. Get me a glass!
噢，我不会那么做的。 我不会偷听我朋友的。
No,I'm not gonna do this,okay? I'm not gonna eavesdrop on my friend.
噢…我爱巴贝多！
I love Barbados.
噢…我不敢相信我在吻你。 我在吻瑞秋啊！
I can't believe I'm kissing you. I'm kissing Rachel!
我知道，我就是她！
I know. I'm her.
瑞秋和乔伊！是瑞秋和乔伊！！！
Rachel and Joey! It's Rachel and Joey!
- 什么？ - 过来这边！
- What? - Get over here!
噢，天呐，我喜欢这些薄墙！
Oh,my God! I love how thin these walls are!
谢谢。
Thank you.
乔伊亲了瑞秋之后
The.One.After.Joey.And.Rachel.Kiss
嘿，之前你说我们是不可能的 为什么又改变主意了？
Hey,before,you said that nothing could happen between us. What changed?
之前这样说是因为罗斯...
Well,I only said that because of Ross.
- 可后来我看见他在吻查莉… - 什么？
- And then I saw him kissing Charlie. - What?
罗斯和查莉？
Ross and Charlie?
哇！ 她真的很想加入到我们中来呢，呃？
Wow! She's really making her way through the group,huh?
- 啊，说这个干吗？ - 啊....
- Eh,who am I to talk? - Yeah.
真不敢相信，瑞秋和乔伊？
I can't believe this. Rachel and Joey?
那边那对恐龙二人组怎么办啊？
How about the dinosaur twins in the other room?
- 那堵墙没人负责啊！ - 有我呢！
- No one is manning that wall! - I'm on it!
- 听到什么了？ - 我想我听见他们在拉窗帘…
- Anything? - I think I hear curtains closing.
我们听到鞋被踢掉了
We've got shoes being kicked off over here.
弹簧床，不会错的！
Bedsprings! Unmistakable!
- 你有想过那是你哥吗？ - 你说出来才想到。找个人来换我啊！
- You realize that's your brother. - Not until you said it. Somebody switch!
等等！
Wow! Wait a minute.
罗斯和查莉，乔伊和瑞秋，
Ross and Charlie. Joey and Rachel.
菲比和麦克！我们是唯一没有换过人的一对呢！
Phoebe and Mike. We're the only ones leaving with the person we came with!
不是啊！我和莫妮卡一起来的 却要和古怪阿尔（恶搞专家扬科维克的外号）一起走。
That's not true. I came with Monica,I'm leaving with Weird Al.
好吧，我受够了这种头发的笑话了。
Okay,I've had it with the hair jokes.
- 明天早上，我们走之前我会去发廊的。 - 好的，荞麦！
- Tomorrow I'm going to the salon. - Okay,Buckwheat.
你们该来听听这个，太棒了… 简直就像是免费的A片！
You gotta hear this,it's great! It's like free porn.
- 呃…怎么啦？ - 对，只是…我想我不能这么做…
- Is everything okay? - It's just.. I don't think I can do this.
噢…是否因为躺在床罩上？
Oh,is it because of what might be on the bed?
- 我也看过那些报道了，在红外线下和... - 不，不！
- I saw that report,with the infrared.. - No! No.
不。
No.
呃，我要跟乔伊谈谈。 你们才刚刚分手。
Look,I need to talk to Joey. I mean,you guys just broke up.
我们之间再发生什么之前 我要确定他不反对。
Before anything more happens between us,I need to know he's okay with it.
- 我，呃…我完全明白。 - 好吧，我想我要去找他了…
- I completely understand. - All right,I'm gonna go find him.
我想…我需要点时间…让我那个…
I just need a second before I can,you know..
外婆…外婆…外婆…
Grandma,Grandma,Grandma.
- 好了，过会儿见。 - 好的…
- Okay,I'll see you later. - Okay!
关门声，他走了…
That's the door. He's gone.
而她…打开了电视…
And she's turning on the TV..
在看…《选美俏佳人》。
and watching Miss Congeniality.
亲爱的，如果你连这都听得到 那你知道的就太多了！
Honey? If you know it through a wall,you know it too well.
嘿，你们干什么呢？
Hey,what are you guys doing?
噢，我们在… 快要走了，我们很伤心 所以在跟这旅馆告别。
We're just.. We're sad to go,so we're just saying goodbye to the hotel.
我爱你…
I love you..
天堂旅店 高尔夫胜地和水浴…
Paradise Hotel Golf Resort and Spa.
对，我们玩得很开心，谢谢！
Yeah. We had a great time,thank you.
再见！
Bye.
呃… 嗨，你们看见乔伊在哪儿了吗？
Okay. Hey,have you guys seen Joey anywhere?
他应该现在在他房间里 和他现任女友查莉在一起。
He's probably in his room with his current girlfriend,Charlie.
这就是我们知道的情况…
That's the situation as we know it.
好吧，如果看到他，告诉他我在找他好吗？
If you see him,could you tell him I'm looking for him?
- 没问题！ - 谢了！
- You got it. - Thanks.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
另一边墙，伙计！另一边！
Other wall,people! Other wall!
- 瑞秋，你在吗？ - 噢天呐，是罗斯啊。
- Rach,you there? - Oh,my God,that's Ross!
- 怎么办？ - 噢，保-保-保持镇静。保持镇静。
- What are we gonna do? - Okay,just be calm.
我们只是随便聊聊。
For all he knows,we're just hanging out.
好吗？ 随意一点。
All right? So just be nonchalant.
- 这不叫随意！ - 我不知道那是什么意思。
- That's not nonchalant! - No idea what it means.
哦…好吧，躲起来！
Okay,just hide.
- 瑞秋? - 来了！试试床下行不行！
- Rach? - Coming! Try under the bed.
床底不够高啊。
There's no room under the bed..
- 出什么事了？ - 没…
- Is everything okay? - Yeah.
- 嘿  - 嗨… - 你知道乔伊在哪儿吗？
- Hey. Do you know where Joey is? - Hi.
我真的不知道…
I really don't.
- 我能和你谈谈吗？ - 当然，可以…
- Can I talk to you for a minute? - Yeah. Sure.
我简直不敢相信…你们一直…
I don't believe this. Have you guys been..?
嘘嘘…趴在墙上好好听。
This is the listening side of the wall.
然后她告诉我她和乔伊分手了
Then she told me that she and Joey had broken up..
某种程度上是因为她对我有感觉。
and part of the reason was she had feelings for me.
呃呃…对…没错…
Right. Yeah.
你知道吗，我碰到查莉的那天就想约她出去。
You know I've wanted to ask Charlie out since the day I met her.
噢，我明白…我知道这对你来说很难。
Oh,I know,I know. That's been really hard for you.
不管怎么样，事情一件接一件，而且…
Anyway,one thing led to another,and..
噢…还没知道是怎么回事，我们接吻了。
before you know it,we were kissing.
你觉得乔伊会多生气？
How angry do you think Joey's gonna be?
这很难说，罗斯。这很难说。
That is hard to say,Ross. That is hard to say.
我要去找他了。他一定就在什么地方。
I gotta find him. He's gotta be here someplace.
就是啊！
You would think.
乔伊!
Joey?
- 他走了吗？ - 你怎么做到的？
- Is he gone? - How are you doing this?
怎么…哇…嘿！
What? Hey!
你们怎么…这是怎么回事？ 你们一直听着吗？
What are you..? What is this? Have you been listening this entire time?
对！
Yeah!
那，这又是怎么回事？
Now,what is this?
啊，这是怎么回事？ 好吧，这么说吧 我们吻了十分钟
What is this? Well,let's see. We kissed for 10 minutes..
然后现在和朋友说这件事 我想只有六年级学生才这样！
and now we're talking to our friends about it,so I guess this is sixth grade.
哦，不…你想过这会变得多复杂吗？
No,no. Have you thought about how complicated this could get?
- 罗斯怎么办? - 可他现在跟查莉在一起。
- What about Ross? - Well,he's with Charlie now.
对，可他想在正式开始之前先和你说一下。
Yeah,but he wants to talk to you before anything really happens with her.
作为朋友，你们不觉得你们也应该这么做吗？
And as his friend,I mean,don't you think he deserves the same from you?
你戳到我痛处了，盖勒！
You're a pain in my ass,Geller.
好吧，很感谢你们的意见
Look,we appreciate all the advice..
但这是我和乔伊之间的事，我们能处理…
but this is between Joey and me. We can handle it.
好吧，我们要回去了，可你能帮我们做件事吗？ 为这些在乎你们的朋友...
We'll go. Will you do one thing for us,the people that care about you?
- 当然… - 去说清楚！
- Sure. - Enunciate.
出去！
Get out!
你觉得怎样？
Are they right?
可能吧，是… 我是说
Probably,yeah. I mean,maybe we should..
我们应该先和他说清楚。
hold off until we talk to Ross.
对…对，我们可以等 我们今天晚上什么事都不做。
Yeah. Yeah. We can wait. We don't have to do anything tonight.
对，我想这样最好…
Yeah,I think that would be best.
那么，那么我要…我要走了…
So,I'm gonna.. I'm gonna take off.
- 除非… - 我喜欢“除非”！
- Although.. - I like "although."
我是说
I mean,you know..
我和罗斯已经有将近…
Ross and I haven't dated in,like..
6年没约会了。
six years.
6年？
Six years?
哇…跟读高中一样久了…
Wow. That's almost as long as high school.
而且，他现在跟查莉在一起。
Plus,you know,he is with Charlie now.
就是啊！
Absolutely.
- 他已经对你没感觉了。 - 是啊。
- He's not thinking about you. - No.
我才对你有感觉...
I'm thinking about you.
对…
Yeah.
- 我们忘了罗斯吧… - 已经忘了。
- Let's forget about Ross. - It's forgotten.
-怎么了？ - 没事…
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
说真的…怎么了？
Seriously,what is it?
没事…真的… 没事…再来…再来…
Nothing. It's really.. It's nothing. Come here. Come here.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
对不起，我只是，呃…
Sorry,I just..
看起来我无法忽略罗斯…
I can't seem to get Ross out of my head.
好吧，让我来帮你忙吧。
Well,maybe I can help.
哦，你的唇真软…再来一次…
Your lips are so soft. Do that again.
你说得对…我们真的要跟罗斯谈谈…
Yeah,we need to talk to Ross. Yeah.
嗨！你们准备好要走了？
Hey. You guys ready to go?
还没。莫妮卡还在发廊，而我还没收拾好。
Not quite. Monica's at the salon,and I'm finishing packing.
伙计！你不打算带上你的圣经吗？
Dude,you're not taking your Bible?
你不应该拿这个走的。
You're not supposed to take that.
而且这是新约，你要它干什么？（犹太人只信旧约）
Besides,it's a New Testament. What are you gonna do with it?
了解耶稣…
Learn about Jesus.
- 嗨！ - 你跟乔伊说过了？
- Hey! - So did you talk to Joey?
呃，没…还没。我找不到她。 我会在飞机上跟他说。
No. I couldn't find him. I'm just gonna talk to him on the plane.
对，听起来不错…盖勒博士！
Okay. Sounds like a good idea,Dr. Geller.
别这么说！
Stop it.
PHD（博士）
Ph.D.
你真淫荡！
You're filthy.
- 嘿，你们见过莫妮卡了吗？ - 呃，我想她去发廊了。
- Hey. Have you guys seen Monica? - Actually,I think she went to the salon.
哦，对，噢，她刚去了发廊…
Oh,yeah. Oh,she went to the salon,all right.
看一下！
Check it out!
谁会最喜欢这个啊？
Whose day just got better?
钱德！
Chandler!
嘿!... 啊啊啊!
Hey!
- 你觉得怎么样？ - 我想…
- What do you think? - I think..
我想我能看见你的头皮。
I think I can see your scalp.
你们不喜欢吗？
Don't you just love it?
对…对…对…你把贝壳挂在头上。
Yeah. Yeah,you got shellfish in your head.
真是太…那个了…去吧女朋友！
It's something. You go,girlfriend.
- 你以前没这么说过是吗？ - 不止一次。
- You never said that in your life. - Not once.
我想也是。
I thought so.
- 菲比？ - 很高兴你这样做了！
- Phoebe? - I'm so glad you did that.
听听这个…
Oh,and listen to this.
你知道吗？…这真是对视觉...和听觉的享受。
What do you know? It's a treat for the eyes and the ears.
哦，噢。哇,我和查莉分手后还要坐在她旁边，太尴尬了。
Wow,it's kind of weird that I'm sitting next to Charlie after we broke up.
就是啊，巴贝多航空真是不关心你的私生活。
Yeah. It's almost as if Air Barbados doesn't care about your social life.
嘿，有人想替我跟查莉坐吗？
Does someone mind switching and sitting with Charlie?
我…嘿！伙计，我跟查莉整个会议都在一起。
Oh,I mean,I.. Dude,I spent the whole conference with Charlie.
- 我了解… - 不，我要的。
- I understand. - No,I'll do it.
我也想跟谁换换。  我真的不想跟阿伦・艾佛森（篮球明星）坐在那儿。
Wish I could switch. I really don't want to sit with Allen lverson over there.
- 嘿！ - 嘿！
- Hey. - Hey.
呃…知道吗，当我们升空 机长关闭系好保险带的标志后…
Once we're in the air and the captain turns off the seat belt sign..
你就可以自由的在我的小屋里遨游了…
you feel free to roam about my cabin.
你检查行李箱的时候要小心
And you should be careful when checking your overhead bins.
- 很容易和别人的搞混的... - 啊…调情你真的不在行…
- Because items may shift during.. - Oh,you're not good at this.
- 今天晚上你非要回家吗？ - 不，我想我可以来过夜的。
- Do you have to go home tonight? - No,I think I could come over.
今天星期六，不是吗？
It's Saturday,right?
怎么了？
What?
- 呃…今晚我不行。 - 为什么？
- I can't do anything tonight. - Why not?
我有约会。
I have a date.
- 你有个…你有个约会？跟谁？ - 噢，是…我女朋友。
- You have a date? With who? - Oh,it's my girlfriend.
- 你有…你有女朋友？ - 对…呃
- You have a girlfriend? - Yeah.
之前我们分手后，我开始约会其他人。
Well,when you and I broke up,I started seeing someone.
- 那...多久了？ - 3个月。
- Well,for how long? - Three months.
3个月?
Three months?
好吧…
Okay.
这可能不关我的事,只是 呃…你认为你还会跟她好多久？
This is none of my business,but how long are you gonna keep seeing her?
今天晚上晚饭的时候，我会告诉她结束了。 我保证。
I'll tell her that it's over tonight at dinner. I promise.
噢，好吧…好的。那你去吧。
Oh,okay,good. You do that.
然后当你回到家 可能会有个特别的邮包在那儿等着你。
When you get home,maybe there'll be a special delivery package waiting for you.
我可能会签收。撕开它。
Maybe I'll sign for it,tear it open.
- 扯开包装材料…. - 你知道吗，我们会做爱。你不用再说了
- Pull out the packing material.. - We'll have sex. Let's leave it there.
这是我们看巴贝多的最后一眼了！
It's our last glimpse of Barbados.
也是我看世间万物的最后一眼。
And my last glimpse of anything.
好吧，我要去和乔伊谈谈。 我想现在是时候了。
All right,I'm gonna go talk to Joey. I think this is the right time.
空姐说完“duty free”(免税)以后他总是情绪很好。 [乔伊听成doody free（随便做）]
He's in a good mood after the flight attendant says "duty-free."
好，祝你好运！
Okay. Good luck.
你知道,如果他不能接受 那我们之间就什么都不能发生
You know,if he's not okay with this then nothing more can happen between us.
我知道。
I know.
如果事情真的那样了我想让你知道...
Well,if that's the case,I just want you to know..
我认为我可能已经爱你非常非常深了
that I think I could have fallen for you really,really hard.
另一方面来说,如果他能接受
On the other hand,if he is okay with us..
那就...你知道...算了,管他呢
then,you know,it's cas,whatever.
罗斯要过来了。 我想现在会是个告诉他的好时候。
Ross is coming over. I think now would be a good time to talk to him.
我想是的。只是…我好紧张啊。
I guess so. I'm just.. I'm really nervous.
好吧，你这样想着： 你说完以后
Well,keep in mind that by the time you're done..
他们就上餐了。
they'll probably be serving dinner.
还紧张吗？
Still nervous?
我要吃意大利面。
I'm gonna get the lasagna.
- 嗨，瑞秋… - 怎么！
- Hey,Rach? - Yeah?
- 介意我在这儿坐一会吗？ - 不介意，当然不！不！
- Do you mind if I sit here for a sec? - Yeah. Yeah,sure. Yeah.
祝你好运！
Good luck.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- Hey. - Hey.
我，呃…
So I..
有点儿关于查莉的事要跟你说。
I kind of need to talk to you about Charlie.
- 好的 - 好吧，昨天晚上你们俩分手以后…
- Yeah? - Last night,after you guys broke up..
当然我觉得很遗憾… 呃
So sorry to hear about that,by the way.
查莉和我倾诉，然后…
Well,Charlie and I were talking,and..
呃
Well..
你们接吻了。
You kissed.
哇…什么？
Wh.. What?
你怎么会这样想的啊？
What? What would give you that idea?
- 我看见了。 - 对，我们是接吻了
- I saw you. - Yeah,we kissed.
不过…什么都没发生，知道吗。
But nothing else. Nothing else happened,okay?
- 罗斯…没关系的。 - 什么？
- Ross,Ross,Ross. It's okay. - What?
这没关系。
It's okay. You know,look..
我完全理解，好吗？ 你们
I totally understand,all right? You guys..
你比我更适合她。你知道吗？ 而且…
make way more sense than her and I ever did,you know? And..
- 我希望你们幸福。 - 真的？
- I want you to be happy. - Are you serious?
当然…
Yeah.
- 我也有点事想说… - 我真是无话可说了…
- Now I have something.. - I am speechless.
你居然把我的幸福放在第一位。 我是说
I mean,the fact that you would put my happiness first like that,I mean..
你真是个令人难以置信的好朋友 你知道吗？
You're an incredible friend,do you know that?
- 噢…呃…呃…在你… - 不，我说真的。
- Well,look,before you go.. - No,I mean it.
你既忠诚，又无私，慷慨…
I mean,you're so loyal,man. And selfless and generous.
我是，当然是。
I am those things,yeah.
你知道吗？我认识钱德更久 我也一直把他作为我最好的朋友
I've known Chandler longer,so I think of him as my best friend. But now..
不过现在… 我想应该重新考虑一下了…
I may have to rethink some stuff.
伙计！
Dude!
嘿，有没有事情我能帮忙的？
Hey,if there is ever anything I can do for you..
暂时还没有…
I can't think of anything.
- 谢谢！ - 没什么！
- Thanks. - Yeah.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- So hi. - Hi.
- 你，呃，你和乔伊谈过了？ - 啊，对。我们聊得很开心。
- So you talked to Joey? - Oh,yeah. We had a really good talk.
- 噢！太棒了！ - 对！
- Oh,that's great. - Yeah.
- 噢，一切都好吗？ - 噢，不，简直太棒了。
- So everything's okay? - Oh,no,it's great.
- 太棒了。他真是…他真是好得让人吃惊。 - 啊…呃，显然我也这么想。
- It's great. He's an amazing guy. - Oh,well,obviously,I think so too.
对，我感到很兴奋。
Well,I'm so excited about this.
真的？兴奋？
Really? Excited?
你开玩笑吗？我现在做梦 都在想着要去干那事…
What,are you kidding? I have had some very dirty dreams about this.
让开！
Excuse me.
你没说是吗？
You didn't tell him,did you?
我没法说。他把我说得天花乱坠。
I couldn't. He was saying all these really nice things about me.
我不想惹火他，收回他说的话。  我快要顶替钱德的位置了。
I didn't want him to get mad and take them back. I'm gonna edge out Chandler!
好吧，好吧！回纽约以后，我跟他说。
Fine. Forget it. When we go back to New York,I will tell him.
谢谢。真的，我很感激。
Thank you. Yeah,I appreciate that.
- 嗨，麦克家。 - 嘿，是麦克。
- Hi,Mike's place. - Hey,it's Mike.
- 噢，真快。 - 噢，呃…不，她还没来。
- That was fast. - Oh,no,she's not here yet.
知道吗，我想我应该走了 我可以在电话上跟她说分手。
You know,I'm just gonna take off and break up with her over the phone.
不，你不能走！快用东西捆住自己！
You can't do that. Oh,come on,Mike,strap on a pair.
你为什么不直接告诉她我们又在一起了。 知道吗，女人欣赏诚实。
Why don't you tell her that we got back together. Women appreciate honesty.
也喜欢轻柔的拍打。
We also appreciate gentle spanking once in a while,just FYl.
还有一件事…  可能…在我的咖啡台上有张珍贵的照片。
One more thing. There might be a picture of Precious on my coffee table.
她叫珍贵?
Her name's Precious?
她是纯种的吗？ 你在兽笼里挑的她？
Is she a pure breed,or did you pick her up at the pound?
- 不管怎么说，我只想让你知道一下。 - 好吧，噢，如果她伤心的话
- I just want to give you a heads up. - Okay. And if she gets upset..
记得挠挠她的肚子，逗她高兴
just scratch her tummy and give her a liver snap.
你知道吗 又一个金发女郎。
What do you know,another hot blonde.
嗨，我是珍贵，你是谁？
Hi. I'm Precious. Who are you?
- 我…我是菲比。 - 菲比？
- I'm Phoebe. - Phoebe?
麦克的前女友菲比？ 他一生所爱的？那个菲比？
Mike's ex-girlfriend,Phoebe? The love of his life? That Phoebe?
很高兴认识你（法语）
Enchante
噢，我真想快让同事们快点看看这个…嗷！
Oh,I can't wait for everyone at work to see these!
- 明天晚上你就要回去工作了是吗？ - 对！
- You go back to work tomorrow night? - Yeah.
那么如果你想让他们看
So if you want people to see them..
也就是说你今晚不会把他们解下啦？
you're not having them taken out,say,at the break of dawn?
呃，如果我解下来了，我就不能这么做了。
Well,if I had them taken out,then I wouldn't be able to do this.
你喜欢的，是吗？
You like that,right?
- 你唱什么呢？ - 《十全十美》里的波利罗舞曲。
- What are you singing? - It's "Bolero" from 10.
那是《现代启示录》里的《狂热的瓦格纳》。
It's "Ride of the Valkyries" from Apocalypse Now.
事情是这样的：这些贝壳是用来解决 你头发的卷曲问题的。
Here's the thing. The cornrows were a solution to your frizzy-hair problem.
而现在我们回家了，我们不再受那个问题困扰了 所以如果你考虑一下…
Now that we're home,you don't have that problem. If you think about it..
我讨厌他们！
I hate them.
- 什么？你说过你喜欢的。 - 我说过吗？我们回想一下。
- What? You said you liked them. - Did I? Let's refresh.
我想我说的是“我可以看见你的头皮”。
I believe what I said was that I could see your scalp.
好吧，那么你不喜欢。可其他人都喜欢。
Well,fine. So you don't like them. Everybody else does.
再想想，让我们回到那次旅游…
Again,let's journey back.
我记得瑞秋说的是 她以前从没注意过你的头骨的形状。
As I recall,Rachel said she had never noticed the shape of your skull before.
还有乔伊… 乔伊当时看不出你有什么不一样。
And Joey? Well,Joey didn't realize there was anything different.
知道吗？我不管。 我喜欢这样，喜欢它，而且我要留着它。
You know what? I don't care. I like it,and I'm gonna keep it.
你嫉妒是因为你的头发不能这么做…嗷！
You're just jealous because your hair can't do this.
- 敲在你的牙上了？ - 还有眼睛！
- Get yourself in the tooth? - And the eye.
嗨…她来了。嗨艾玛。 噢，天呐，我想死你了。
Hi! There she is! Hi,Emma. Oh,my God,I missed you.
哦，艾玛，我真是太想你了，嗨！
Oh,Emma,I missed you so much. Hi.
嘿…你和外婆过得开心吗？呃？
Did you have a good time with Grandma Greene? Huh?
她喋喋不休的时候给你兴奋剂了吗？
Did she give you a bottle of antidepressants again to use as a rattle?
只有一次，罗斯，而且只有5毫克。
That was one time,Ross,and they were only,like,five milligrams.
噢，嘿，艾玛，爸爸有礼物带给你。 知道吗？
Hey,Emma,Daddy has some presents for you,okay?
我想让你在这儿等一会儿， 等等，宝贝儿。
I want you to wait right here.Come here,sweetie.
呃…罗斯 事实上我有点儿事要跟你说。
Ross,actually,there's something that I really need to talk to you about.
好的，说吧！
Okay,shoot.
- 好吧，呃…好的，事情是这样的。 - 哦不！
- Okay. All right,here's the deal. - Oh,no!
- 怎么了？那是什么？ - 噢，大瓶的洗发液破了！
- What is it? - Oh,major shampoo explosion!
- 呃，听着罗斯，这很难开口。 - 啊！！还沾得到处都是。
- Look,Ross,this really isn't easy. - Oh,it's all over everything!
为什么？为什么偏偏是我？
Why? Why me?
因为你拿了300瓶洗发液？
Because you took 300 bottles of shampoo?
我想所有的事情都跟我作对.
I guess things were just going too well for me.
对不起，对不起。你刚才说什么？
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. You were saying?
- 好吧，呃…好吧，听着，是关于我和… - 噢，不要，又一瓶
- Well,yeah. Look,it's about me and.. - Oh,not another one!
噢，天…是摩丝。这个更难清理！
Oh,my God.. Oh,and this is moisturizer! It's even harder to clean!
为什么？为什么坏事总是落到好人的头上？
Why? Why do bad things happen to good people?
- 哇！好吧，很显然这不是个好时候。 - 嗯，你觉得呢
- Wow. Clearly this is not a good time. - You think?
好的，再见。
Okay. Bye.
好了，麦克已经回来了。
All right,so Mike's on his way over.
知道吗，你以为你们在这儿见 他却以为在餐馆见面
You thought you were meeting here,he thought at the restaurant,so..
所以…谁对谁错不重要 重要的是…我要走了。
It doesn't matter who's right or wrong. The point is,I'm gonna take off.
你告诉我到底发生了什么之前 我不会让你走的。
Wait. I'm not letting you leave until you tell me what's going on. I mean..
我是说，你们和好了还是怎么了？
are you guys getting back together or something?
好吧…
All right.
苏茜，我能叫你苏茜吗？
Susie.. Can I call you Susie?
我叫珍贵。
My name is Precious.
对，可我叫不出口。
I can't say that.
呃…苏茜，我想跟你直说…
Susie,I'm gonna be straight with you.
麦克和我和好了… 并且，呃…不幸的是
Mike and I are back together. And unfortunately..
这样就要终结你们的关系。
that effectively ends your relationship with him.
并且他对此感到很抱歉，并祝你好运。
He's very sorry about that,and wishes you the best luck in all your endeavors.
我无法相信…为什么？
I just can't believe this. Why?
- 这个我也不知… - 噢，他为什么这么做？
- Well,I don't.. - Why would he do this?
- 我做错什么了？ - 没有，你什么也没做错。
- What's wrong with me? - There's nothing wrong with you.
我是说，现在我到底该做什么？
What the hell am I supposed to do now?
可恶！你这女人，镇定点，镇定。
Damn it,woman! Pull yourself together!
保持你的尊严，看在上帝的份上！
Have some pride,for the love of God!
好吧，你好象不喜欢苦涩的爱情。
Okay,not a fan of the tough love.
我真不明白，为什么他不给我点暗示在先呢！
I just can't believe that Mike didn't give me any warning.
他之前也不知道的 他本来没计划到巴贝多向我求婚的…
He didn't know. He wasn't planning on coming to Barbados and proposing to me.
他向你求婚了？ 我这个生日真是糟透了。
He proposed to you? This is the worst birthday ever!
听着，珍贵…
Look,Precious..
你不值得为麦克伤心。 你是个迷人的、聪明的女孩
Mike's not worth this. You're an attractive,intelligent woman..
你看 麦克简直有点混蛋。
and let's face it,Mike's kind of a wang.
我是说 他向我求婚的时候甚至还跟你在一起…
He proposed to me while he was still seeing you.
他居然想在你生日的时候跟你分手？
He was gonna break up with you on your birthday?
并且，我本来也不想说的 不过这个周末他对你不忠的太多了。
I don't like to kiss and tell,but he cheated on you a lot this weekend.
噢，天呐，可能你说对了。 可能我并不需要他。
Oh,my God,you know,maybe you're right. Maybe I don't need him.
我应该受到尊重。
I deserve to be treated with respect.
你这个混蛋，麦克。 你这个胆怯的杂种，我希望你烂死在地狱里。
Screw you,Mike. You're a coward and a bastard,and I hope you rot in hell!
不用谢我！
You're welcome.
亲爱的，你在里面好久了…没事吧？
Honey? You've been in there for a long time. Is everything okay?
有一点事。
Not really.
我出事了。
I have a problem.
是吗？怎么了？
Really? What happened?
好吧，我唱着《没有女人哭泣》跳舞...
Well,I was dancing around and singing "No Woman,No Cry"..
然后就挂住了。
and I got stuck.
- 一点都动不了？ - 噢，不，我可以动…
- You can't move at all? - Oh,I can move.
如果我解开你，你会解开这个玉米垄发型吗？
If I untangle you,will you please get rid of the cornrows?
我想会…
I guess so.
- 有些看起来缠在一起了。 - 对，我自己试着解开过。
- Some of these look a little frayed. - Yeah,I tried to gnaw myself free.
- 嗨！ - 嗨！
- Hey. - Hi.
- 呃…你跟罗斯说了吗？ - 没有，我想说
- So? Did you tell Ross? - Well,I tried..
但他的洗发液出事故了。
but then he had a shampoo-related emergency.
- 所以我想该轮到你去了。 - 不，不，不，不，不，不，不，不…
- So I guess now it's your turn again. - No,no,no,no.
我想最好是你去告诉他，知道吗  这对女人来说容易些。
I think it's better if you tell him. You know,it's easier for a woman.
你知道，如果他抓狂了 你就可以…
That way,you know,if he gets mad,all you have to do is go:
我不是有意的。
"I didn't mean it.
我太抱歉了。
I'm so sorry."
对，我们的确会这么做的
Yeah,because that's what we do.
好吧，好吧，这样，呃…这样，这样怎么样？
All right,all right,okay. How about this? How about this? Tomorrow..
明天…明天我们一起去，一起告诉他。
Tomorrow we'll both go and we'll tell him together.
好吧，听起来公平些。
Okay,that sounds fair.
- 可这样我们又不能… - 我知道，我知道…
- That just means,once again,we can't.. - I know.
不过没问题。 我们有自制力，我们不是动物啊。
That's okay. I mean,we can control ourselves. We're not animals.
- 当然，当然我们可以等。 - 是啊。
- No! Of course,we can wait. - Yeah.
那么我想该说晚安了？
All right,so I guess that means good night then.
好的！晚安！
Yep. Good night.
晚――安！
Good night.
晚安！
- 说真的，晚安！ - 别说晚安了。
- Seriously,good night. - Stop saying good night.
真对不起啊...
I'm so sorry.
看我在抽屉里找到了什么…
Look what I found in the drawer.
你还说我永远不会戴它呢。
And you said I'd never wear this.
我把你解救下来，你还没报答我呢？
Now that I untangled you,how about you do a little something for me?
-当然，你想让我怎么报答？ - 你应该知道的啊。
- Sure. What did you have in mind? - I think you know.
- 真的？但我有点不想啊。 - 我就是想要。
- Really? I don't.. I don't really feel like it. - This is what I want to do.
好吧。
Okay.
我不知道你为什么这么喜欢它。
I just don't get why you like it so much.
她是个联邦特工，还参加选美呢（《选美俏佳人》）。
She's an FBI agent posing as a beauty contestant!